you stop?
We'll go there to the place
We'll go there to the place Dreaming on!
I'm so dumb, I'm so dumb.
I'm going to fight, I'm so dumb.
I'm loving my self-serve.
I'll be dreaming on!
Whoa-oh!
Whoa! Whoa-oh!
Really kept me waiting!
Yo-ho!
TJ!
Everyone, from this day forward,
I'm officially a Straw Hat!
We were all so worried about you!
Mr.
T, the boss is back!
I'm relieved as well.
Seems you've had quite the struggle.
It's wild we have a former
warlord of the sea on our crew.
You're gonna kick so much ass.
I'm so glad he's all right.
Nami, could you please don't
know the intimacy of that hug?
I was really worried about you, man.
It took a while. My apologies.
Some of the sun pirates were wounded,
so I had to tend to them first.
Then they threw me a big
send-off for old time's sake.
Forgive me, Captain.
But you know how it is.
Everyone, thank you for having me.
And once again, I shall do my best.
You won't believe this
guy's steering skills.
Jinbei, you gotta show off!
He even used the Sunny
like a big surfboard.
Freakin' sweet!
It's about time.
We finally got a guy who can make
full use of the ship of dreams.
Let's do this!
Time for a toast, right?
Oh yeah!
Now let's drink!
Hold up a second We don't have
any alcohol on hand, though.
Wrong.
I can smell some booze in the air.
Then where the hell is it?
Right over there.
Hey!
Sir Luffy!
If you have a moment,
I would like to discuss our next course
of action once we reach the island.
You hear me?
Please, make your way over to us.
Sir Luffy!
You're lying your ass off.
All I can smell is the ocean.
I am NOT a liar!
I smell food over that way!
Please, Sir Luffy!
Give it up.
There's no point in trying
to reason with them.
They're not gonna listen to you.
Besides, you bums are on my ship.
If you want to talk
strategy, take it elsewhere.
Please excuse my tardiness.
I wish to be briefed on your strategy.
Oh-ho!
Sir Full Power Cecilion! Duke Dogstorm,
I know that Ugarra will be fighting
as a retainer for the Kozuki clan.
Therefore, allow me to lead the big
forces in your stead, sir. Splendid.
Thank you, Karoo.
Allow me as well.
It would be my humble honor to assist you.
I will take command over the samurai.
Boss Yoguro, it's you.
You must forgive my lengthy disappearance.
I know that you have suffered.
I am delighted to see you as well.
Now, before we reach our destination,
let's work out the details
of our plan, shall we?
I trust you have everything in order?
Of course!
Those bastards.
Look at them making themselves
right at home on my deck.
Gentlemen, I only have time to
explain this plan once, so heed well.
Let's take a glance at the map.
Onigashima is a remote island
surrounded by mountains.
Even if you attempt to proceed by boat,
the steep mountainside will bar your way.
It's impenetrable!
There is but a single
entrance to the entire island,
and that would be through the front gate.
The Giant Skull is a rock
formation surrounded by mountains,
with Kaido's castle hidden inside.
Referencing the blueprints
that we had stolen,
there is a rear entrance located
on the opposite side of the island.
Understand?
Our best bet is to avoid the
heavily guarded front gate entirely.
Therefore,
we shall separate into two groups,
take the mountain paths to the left
and right, then infiltrate from behind.
Kaido will be intoxicated after the
festivities, so we'll make it quick.
It'll be a surprise attack.
We cannot fail!
That's rather impressive.
That was the decoy plan you set in
Kanjuro's presence to deceive him, right?
Though the details are
a bit hastily crafted,
it will surely serve its
purpose and throw off the enemy.
Decoy?
Now, what is the real strategy?
He's over-evaluating again.
Firstly, you have to assume
the enemy is aware of the raid.
And they'll actively seek out the
Akazaya Samurai before anyone else.
They'll also be looking for me.
Since we're all captains, that goes
for Straw Hat and Eustass as well.
Indeed, that is true.
Honestly, it won't matter what
kind of plan you slap together.
We're dealing with two
Carrot idiots as allies.
We'll charge straight in no matter what.
No!
But if we use them as decoys,
we can salvage the operation.
Lucky for us, they can hold their own.
Once Kaido finds out he's been invaded,
he's going to send out everything
he's got to stop those two dumbasses.
I understand now!
So when our pirate friends undoubtedly
run straight for the entrance,
the guards will leave the rest
of the palace relatively clear!
Right.
We'll use that opportunity to proceed
down the side paths as planned.
However, that too is a diversion
to protect the samurai.
We're prepared for anything.
Even if we need to sacrifice ourselves,
the Akazaya samurai must make
it to the battle against Kaido.
That's the only thing that matters.
I agree, but how will you
gotta get them inside?
They'll go by water.
Forgetting a detail?
Won't the whirlpools be an issue for us?
That part's already covered.
There's no need to worry.
We're going to use the
Polar Tang, my submarine.
By taking it around the back of the island,
we'll avoid the whirlpools altogether.
Then I'm up.
I'll use my room ability to
send you all onto the island.
Sir Law, thank you.
But there's one concern.
I feel that at the very least, I
must be there to lead the troops.
You have a point.
Then we should send
one of us on each path.
I will take the one side of the
mountain, and you can take the other.
What say you? Raizo? Kawamatsu?
Dogstorm? Kikunojo? Ashura?
I agree.
In the meantime, the rest of
us will all stick together.
We'll make sure to save our full
strength for the fight against Kaido.
Very good.
Just as I planned it.
We'll go with this strategy.
Very clever, Keen.
Incredible plan.
Yeah, Keen.
See the Dorry Gate here?
That's the first hindrance we'll
face when we enter Onigashima.
How serious is this?
Are there guards involved?
Yes, and that isn't all.
It serves as both an entrance and
a small armed fortress for Kaido.
They should have plenty
of cannons to fire at us.
Keep in mind, today is the fire festival.
More beast pirates than usual
will be waiting on Onigashima.
I see, so proceed cautiously.
We don't know how many
of them are expecting us.
I suggest we stick together.
That way if we're found,
we still have a chance.
This sounds risky.
No matter the case.
We must inform our allies of this at once.
Hey.
Where in the hell did
the Straw Hat's boat go?
No!
Oh no, Sir Luffy!
Please don't tell me that was them!
Quickly, sir-law!
Send your vessel that way!
They must be in dire need of assistance!
All right, now, Com-Cum!
Up there!
Don't let them get any closer! Fire!
Blast them away! Take it!
Oh, God!
I'm not there!
Don't go pistol!
It's over for you!
Two-sword style.
Now, Hawkwave!
It seems you have me surrounded.
Time to take him out!
Not so solid.
Swallow Thunder!
Oh!
Now, me who flew, gigantesca model!
And stomp!
My sweet ramen.
Hey, suit guy!
Think you can just light
a cigarette mid-fight?
Ah!
Ah! Ah!
Flanchez!
Yeah!
Franky!
Fucking!
Super!
I think they're doing just
fine without our help. Agreed?
All right, decent fighting, man.
It was all right.
Yes, acceptable. Good job,
troops. Adequate work.
Why'd you guys just wait
on the sidelines, huh?
The Dorry gate guards, they
were all knocked out. Oh, wow.
That's a lot of weapons.
Imagine if we'd fought them.
Our number of troops would
have dwindled down for sure.
Then that means we can
all sail forth together.
To Onigashima!
That was a ton of good
alcohol you just wasted!
Oh, Lord Archie, you'll
never catch up to me!
I won't?
Well, here I come, my pretty!
Seems like someone's in a good mood today.
I like it when you're happy, Mr. Shogun.
It's adorable!
I bet something really
nice happened to you.
What clever girls you all are!
How did you know?
Oh boy, tell us!
Well, it's a most splendid day.
There was some trash in my way and
it's finally been disposed of, you see.
Now that garbage is finally in
the ground where it belongs.
So you're extra happy today because
somebody took the garbage out?
The Shogun is such a weirdo sometimes!
Do you lovely ladies
really find it that odd?
Obviously!
But it's cute in a quirky way! Yeah!
As the shogun of Wano, I declare that
it is now a lord to come to daddy!
Which of you dare to defy my orders?
You, where the hell is my Ashiruko?
I apologize for the delay, sir.
We'll bring it to you right
after we deliver Big Mom's order.
Big Mom?
Why does she get to skip the line?
Did you forget there's gonna be a
performance for the banquet tonight?
I'm a little foggy here.
Why don't you remind me who's the star?
The man's name is right
on the tip of my tongue.
Queen!
Yeah!
Damn right it's me!
And which lead performer's
got the pipes and the talent?
Queen!
That's for sure.
Can you dig it?
So feed me.
I can't lose any more weight.
The ladies will go crazy.
Wipe that stupid grin off
your face and get moving!
The party's in full swing, and
everyone's having a great time. Agreed.
And I'm really looking forward
to the big show tonight, sir.
Do we know if he's joining us? Who?
I'm talking about my son.
He needs to be there!
It's the banquet!
I'll find him, sir!
Commander!
All six members of the Toby
Rope have just arrived!
Are you ready?
They're here to see me.
I might as well introduce them to Lin-Lin.
Where the hell is the old bag, anyway?
It's not a good time, sir.
Big Mom is changing into her
kimono at this moment. What?
Commander Kaido!
The Toby Rope are outside.
Bring them to me!
Ugh!
I don't know.
The Brachio of the tiptoes like a mofo,
no need to be vague, you
know him as the plague!
Coming to you in widescreen!
It's Conney!
I keep you waiting!
Give it up, give it up!
You ready to kick off the Golden Festival?
It's time to party!
Not gonna lose no weight,
just more to appreciate.
I got enough fans attracted to my funk!
Yeah!
I look round as a ball, but
all of this is muscle, y 'all!
These bomb-ass moves of
mine are powered by my...
Y 'all are right on the gotcha ball!
Let me hear you scream!
Now you know how this goes!
I'ma do a little roll call, y 'all!
Now make some noise!
It's your time, not a moment later What
you say, are you sick of waiting, waiters?
Yeah!
You're down to the dumps,
but life is your treasure.
Come on, laugh it at pleasures!
Bless with the gift of smiles and clothes.
Gifters, let it all out!
The headliners know they're
the cream of the crop.
Let me hear your call out from the top!
Last but not least, top six of the face.
Strong and dangerous like my slow.
Give it up, y 'all, for Z-Toby-Rabba!
Ah, psych!
Those pretentious asses never respond.
They stayed under how I can lose.
Now where my monsters at?
No, let's go!
You hearing this shit show?
What do I care?
Orochi's forces, pick it up!
Gonna need the Mimawari
Koby to raise the roof!
No, the only one but you!
But wait, there's more!
I hear we have some
special guests tonight.
Y 'all ready for a family reunion?
Big Mom's kids are on the way!
Queen won't shut his big fat face.
Did you hear him call us a bunch of asses?
He's ever, ever so awful!
So is that your new thing now?
Trying to sound like a fancy lady?
Give it up, it's embarrassing.
Aw, don't be such a booger, Papa!
Don't call me that!
It's ever, ever so lame!
Suppose old queen happened
to drop dead tonight,
there'd be a lead performer vacancy.
Who would it go to?
Answer him, Drake!
You think you're the
most qualified, right?
I'm not interested in
becoming a lead performer.
Don't be stupid!
Oh, you dropping out of the race?
Because that would work
out perfectly for me.
Much obliged, and what about you?
Pay, pay, you passing? Huh?
I don't think you got
the chops since you let
Sobermask get away without
so much as a scratch.
You take that back!
If you insult my sweet Papa one more time,
I'll snap you like a twig - Stop it, sis!
Fine!
You don't get to boss me around!
Calm down!
You think you can tell me what to do, huh?
Hey, that's enough
screeching, you damn crats.
I find their antics rather charming.
I love it when Ellie throws a tantrum.
She's out for blood.
So are we just waiting around, or
did they call us here for a reason?
The usual, I'm sure.
We were told it was urgent.
Kaido's orders.
Take a guess what he wants.
So it's dysfunctional family junk again?
Is Kaido stupid or something?
Don't trash talk the commander, idiot!
Get him on! Over here!
We beat up some guys!
I was hoping we'd have more leeway.
Yo, Mosshead! Huh? Huh?
Where the hell did that come from?
Didn't I tell you?
I know that smell anywhere.
He's like an animal. Hey! It's Freddy!
Come on, you guys, hurry up!
Coming!
We've got a toast to me!
Luffy!
Come on, we're going to drink
it all before you get here!
Or Zoro will.
No, I won't!
I'm on my way!
Here's one for you, boss.
Thank you, Godly.
Raise a toast to Koby, the super
houndsman we've all been waiting for.
Aw, if we had some more
time, I'd break out a song.
You know, exchanging sake cups
is usually a more solemn affair.
All right, get your cups
ready, guys. Cheers! Cheers!
Koby, we're so glad you came back our way.
Thank you for your assistance, Sir Luffy.
You have cleared our
first obstacle for us.
And now we go forward!
You see that?
Since when are they so excited?
If I had to guess,
seeing that fortress dismantled
must have boosted everyone's morale.
Once we get to Onigashima, I bet
they're really gonna lead loose.
Hurry up and finish the toast already!
We gotta get moving so
we can back them up!
We must not let this
opportunity go to waste.
Let's keep up the momentum.
Right.
Our foes will never see us coming.
How lucky we are.
The Straw Hats are quite
an asset. They are.
My despair has been washed away at last.
Now we're carried on the
waves of hope that they bring.
To arms, loyal samurai!
Take a stand as a Kozuki warrior!
We shall lead you!
All ships to Onigashima!
Our moment is now!
What's going on with you?
Luffy.
Why are you being so weird?
Drop the drinks.
Save it for the samurai.
The beast, the toast, everything.
Let's do it after we beat Kaido.
And we'll kick Uruji
and Big Mom's ass, too.
Two, after all this is over, we can
have the biggest, best party ever!
Let's go win this thing!
You know, you're the one who wanted
to stop and have the stupid toast.
But sure, it changed
our plans last second.
That's right.
You tell him, Nami.
Tell me what?
I don't see why you guys are surprised.
He does what he wants.
There's no point in us
complaining about it.
Hey, why are you nodding, too?
It seems that the captain has spoken,
but how do you feel about
delaying the party boss?
I'm pretty sure you
already know my answer!
We're in!
All right!
Let's get a move on!
Follow those samurai!
I am captain!